GAHYUN ELENA YI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Utrecht, the Netherlands | +31 6 8718 9359 kunstvanelena@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Github | Portfolio

"I strive to create products that are not only scalable and efficient but also have engaging, pixel-perfect user experience. Currently seeking an opportunity to leverage my creativity, technical expertise, and passion for coding to contribute to a dynamic software development team."

SKILLS

Front-end: JavaScript(ES6), React, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Bulma, NPM, Webpack, Git, VS Code

Design : Figma, Photoshop, InDesign, Wireframing, User Experience **Work skills :** Collaboration, Communication, Continuous learning

PROJECTS

DoodleyPainter: Developed a web-app inspired by famous drawing toy Etch-a-sketch, that users can create pixel art. Built with vanilla Javascript.

Bookiit: A web app to store a list of books that are read or to be read. Built with vanilla Javascript using ES6 Classes.

elena-yi.dev: Designed and built a personal website from scratch. Focused on ensuring responsiveness and accessibility, delivering an exceptional user experience and pixel perfect layout.

RecipeBind: Started from personal needs, currently building a recipe template app that users can put details of their recipes to save & print them in PDF files.

EDUCATION

2021 User experience design by Google | Coursera

2022 The complete Javascript course by Jonas Schmedtmann | Udemy

2023 Modern React with Redux by Stephen Grider | Udemy

2023 Fullstack Javascript | The odin project (Open Source learning)

2017 Front-end web, Exchange program | Australian National University, Canberra, Australia

2019 Woodworking & Furniture Design, Bachelors of Design | Hongik University, Seoul, Korea

LANGUAGE

English: Bilingual proficiency, Dutch: Limited working proficiency, Korean: Native

WORK EXPERIENCE

04. 2022 - 08. 2023 Sales Advisor, IKEA, Amersfoort, the Netherlands

06. 2021 - 12. 2021 Interior Designer, WellHome, Utrecht, the Netherlands

07. 2019 - 07. 2020 Interior Designer, NEXIS Design, Seoul, Korea

INTEREST

Travelling, Reading, Drawing, Baking, Yoga, Concert, Nature